the justified and has charged up former
c_i_a_ officer
are john and tour kalo
steeple player is said that right
arbiter reiterates problems they write
me anyway out with a espionage act
now that's a very very serious charge
you know that before president obama
there's only been
three instances of the united states
government
charging someone with espionage act
forgiving excessive information
as they claim
this former c_i_a_ officer there
and
six different tastes
that is a special on it because
president or bob promise to
i'd be air and friend to whistle blowers
entrance passage
there's something wrong in our
government he reported he was going to
help you
doesn't look like he's albania
so whatever sag ideal while he talked
about
how we want a quart of people
and how was torture
now he thought it was justified even did
an interview on sixty minutes
and said
uh... that he thought it worked the
underplayed amount of george but we did
but do you happen to call it torture
now they look at that missy i did not
like that
furthermore there was a two thousand a
new york times story which invade
believe he is the source of the dam
proving at and so they say well okay i
got past and i jack i guess you're you
know
there was one of the toughest laws we
have
and we're company get your are part of
the spaces
because it's if
here's a great irony of that
if you actually do the waterboarding if
you didn't torture
you got no punishment whatsoever
now present all mama claimed it was
torture and ridiculous and he says he
stopped at
as ridiculous in a squabble right
is torture
but he didn't always scot-free
the president will not
look backward euler look for work
if you report the waterboarding the
torture
espionage act
when i play with a look back work
all its to protect the c_i_a_'s after
this thing
protect that's the bush administration
error and dick cheney that order that
torture well then of course you look
backward and in fact new uh... looked
very deep into you know us info about
charging
the defense lawyers at one time all back
our whole system is based on
an adversarial system
where somebody gets a defects
now one of the press uh... tactics was
to look at that
interrogators
and try and determine who they were so
they can bring them in the court
and say eight use them as witnesses
because the guys who aren't going to
have a bank
that are face execution
listen when you get an executed we
should be able to call the witnesses
and what they do
obviously for intimidation purposes
eric holder
jeremy just martin said well let's look
into their words are
and say we need to be made and say that
maybe will charge you with that
whatever kind of laws we invited to go
out to you mercifully they have decided
that in our liberty system we're not
going to charge the president is
defense attorneys
but when it comes to a former c_i_a_
officer
but cipher vengeance
meanwhile
heroes they could be a who was one of
the guys who was tortured
he was a u_s_ citizen
he was locked up in the u_s_ first over
three years
no charges
i flipped out over that
at the time
on the interest because i said if they
can do with the jose padilla
they need to do it to anybody he was
here in the united states
and he's a u_s_ citizen
well before circuit this rule yes
bigoted anybody
uh... jose p_b_s_ case against our us
all this thrown out we're not even a
consider whether you were tortured did
the sensory deprivation has set a route
and forget the torture part of it they
just didn't even give you a hearing for
over three years
allowing him listen you got no
right-wing rosso highbury
by the way the people who defended
rumsfeld there of course eric holder
and the justice department
for a couple of blackboard to see if
they did anything wrong they arrest and
indefinitely detain u_s_ citizen without
charges who can we decide that the law
hysteria a little while ago
more enough course ever take the bush
administration of course that they run
spelled
but if you saw what was actually blowing
the whistle spoke with catches
well why is that
once again that was a fairness in that
there isn't it
they look backward when they wanted to
protect the bush administration
and i look forward when they wanted to
is a good thing we voted for change
now of all that weren't bad enough grain
reward points out the third hypocrisy
here
there was a incident inha defect or act
in two thousand five
where uh... murray staff sergeant of
frank would a rich
uh... sp told his soldiers to split is
very sad to say
but should first pass questions later
hasn't direct quote
and they did they killed twenty-four on
armed civilians
so massive
uh... well don't worry uh... they've
really dealt with a major struck a plea
deal with them
where he might get upto
three months in prison
maybe up to three months in prison
twenty-four armed civilians dead
and it's because
they told the marines there
shoot first don't bother let's see if
there is a millions
so if you don't twenty four people
you might get up to the three must and
by the way
uh... let's be fair here
he could also lose two-thirds of the spe
any could be demoted a private
why are
we really got up
but he told world about our clients
are transgressions our problems
when we're coming to get you
espionage a
maza here hussein
has a great quote on this going very
well pointed that out as well
he said below traveling manning true
really consider committee so more crimes
and sort of exposing them
i mean no truer words have ever been
spoken
but what does that say about our u_s_
government
is a bradley many headquarters somebody
water somebody made even shot on armed
civilians have committed war crimes we
would do a walk but most of protective
because he exposed a war crimes
we're doing it are almost
the prosecutor and perhaps put 'em in
jail for the rest of us life
what happened in the united states of
america
and what happened to that change we
voted for